<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Index on raggaer.dev</title><link>https://raggaer.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Index on raggaer.dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:27:36 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://raggaer.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://raggaer.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 20:27:36 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://raggaer.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Álvaro Carvajal Castro Home / Projects mail@raggaer.dev TeamTime backend laravel go php Saas application developed using Laravel and Go. Allows remote team local time synchronization and time tracking. Using beanstalk, cloudfront and lambda for the backend. RavenQuest backend blockchain go polygon solidity P2E Crypto MMORPG Backend developed using Go. Contracts developed using Hardhat with Solidity. Deployed on Polygon PoS with multi-chain support. Read More Ravendawn backend go xenforo paypal coinbase MMORPG Website backend developed using Go.</description></item><item><title>Ravenquest</title><link>https://raggaer.github.io/projects/ravenquest/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 02:05:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://raggaer.github.io/projects/ravenquest/</guid><description>Álvaro Carvajal Castro Home / RavenQuest mail@raggaer.dev 01. RavenQuest RavenQuest is a Play2Earn blockchain game, where users can buy land and build their own game. RavenQuest Whitepaper. Backend made using Go. Website made using server-side rendering. Since RavenQuest is a Play2Earn blockchain game, the backend needs to integrate some blockchain elements in it: Multiple smart-contract using abigen bindings integration. NFT minting on-demand. Link between user-created accounts and their wallets, signing a message and verifying the ownership of the given address.</description></item><item><title>SimpleMixer</title><link>https://raggaer.github.io/projects/simple-mixer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 02:05:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://raggaer.github.io/projects/simple-mixer/</guid><description>Álvaro Carvajal Castro Home / SimpleMixer mail@raggaer.dev https://github.com/Raggaer/simple-mixer 01. SimpleMixer SimpleMixer is a simple centralized Ethereum mixer that uses EIP-712 signatures for withdrawing funds. Users are able to deposit funds into the contract but they need a signature from the central server in order to retrieve the funds back. The central server will emit a new EIP712 signed message. The user can now use that signature from a different public address to interact with the contract withdraw method.</description></item></channel></rss>